

ALDO ALGHIFARI

Software Engineer

SUMMARY

Specialize in crafting responsive web applications using a diverse tech stack including CSS, Bootstrap Framework, JavaScript, React JS, Node JS, PHP, and the Laravel Framework. Experiences in utilizing RDBMS such as MySQL and Oracle. Can work in a team as well as individually, interested to learn new things related to technology.

EXPERIENCES

PT. TOYOTA MOTOR MANUFACTURING

(November 2021 - November 2023)

Diagnosed and resolved machine malfunctions, minimizing production downtime and maintaining production goals

PT. NT PISTON RING INDONESIA

(June 2019 - June 2021)

- Monitored production processes and identified quality issues.
- Analyzed and optimized production processes to reduce production costs

PT. AT INDONESIA

(June 2017 - June 2019)

Set up and operated a variety of CNC machines, including lathes, milling machines

EDUCATION

(2022 - Now)

Horizon University Indonesia
Informatics

(2013 - 2016)

Vocational High School 1 Karawang
Automobile Technology

LICENCES

- Course Software Engineering (RevoU)
- Learn Programming Fundamentals (Dicoding)
- Learn JavaScript (Dicoding)
- Learn SQL (Dicoding)
- Learn Basic AWS Cloud (Dicoding)
- · Learn Git & Github (Dicoding)

CONTACT

- +62 85717912710
- mact-portfolio-aldo.vercel.app
- aldoalghifari24@gmail.com
- Karawang, West Java, Indonesia